# Bryan Burnett

## Software Engineer

#### Contact

Petaluma, California
(707) 241-3005
bryanburnettbmb@gmail.com
linkedin.com/in/bryan-burnett
github.com/crankyhippo
bryanburnett.com

#### About Me

I am proficient in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Creating projects using technology is my passion. Over the last decade I've produced, edited, and hosted my own content about all aspects of technology. This has led me to be a Jack of all trades, and an adaptable problem solver.

### Education

Full Stack Program | Thinkful March - September 2021

## Skills

- JavaScript
- Express
- HTML5 / CSS3
- REST APIs
- React
- UX / UI
- jQuery
- PostgreSQL
- Node.js
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Video Editing
- Graphic Design

## Work Experience

## Production Operator at Google ASG (2021 - Present) Mountain View, CA

- Execute flawless end-to-end event services, by managing client requests, and delegating needs to crew.
- Subject matter expert conducting team training on new equipment and software best practices.
- Communicate standards and create standard operating procedures as technology and scope evolves.

# Operations Tech at Facebook FNTech (2018 - 2021) Menlo Park, CA

- Achieved global impact by creating a support index site for tracking campus logistics, equipment, and capabilities of Facebook's worldwide offices.
- Accomplished numerous successful high priority and high stress company all hands streaming events.
- Consolidated technical knowledge by creating operation procedures documents for onboarding techs and training on a variety of technology.

# Producer at This Week in Tech (TWiT) TWiT (2011 - 2017) Petaluma, CA

- Fluent with publishing to multiple online platforms while adhering to web standards, and followed SEO best practices for publishing content on tight deadlines.
- Managed signal flow and execution of live shows, setup streams, and diagnosed computer network issues.
- Host of "how-to" show, explaining complex projects, ranging from DIY quad copter builds, 3D printing, programming Arduinos with C++, all while keeping the subject matter easy to follow.



# Pomodoro Timer github.com/CrankyHippo/pomodoro-timer

- Built a time interval application based off of the Pomodoro technique allowing the user to pause, play or change the amount of time.
- Designed to test my ability to work with rendering and state management using React.
- Install packages via NPM, run tests from the command line, and debug React code.